Kevin Flynn

NodeJS / VueJS Web Developer

London, UK 07796977257 flynny85@gmail.com www.kubedev.co.uk www.github.com/k-flynn-webdev

INTRO

Naturally curious problem solver. After almost 10 years of experience in the games industry as a technical animator helping both animators and artists be more productive with custom tools and workflow improvements. I've now found a passion in web development.

EXPERIENCE

Studying — Web Development

july 2018 - present

Full-stack development

Freelance — Technical Animator

Jan 2017 - jan 2018

22 Cans, Guildford, UK — *Technical Animator*

July 2015 - Jan 2017

Mobile titles - Animator

If You Can, London, UK — Technical Animator

May 2013 - March 2015

Mobile titles - Animator

Traveller's Tales, Wilmslow, UK — Technical Animator

Jun 2008 - Apr 2013

Various Lego titles - Animator

EDUCATION

The University of Bolton - 2002 / 2006.

- BA Graphic Design & Illustration.

SKILLS

- Design/Mockup
- Responsive Design
- Html/CSS/Javascript
- Animation (3d)

TECHNOLOGIES

- NodeJS (ExpressJS)
- VueJS
- MongoDB
- Nginx
- VPS Deploy
- Testing (Mocha/Chai)
- Unity
- C# (Unity)
- Python

PROJECTS

BS-Bingo Github.

An easy to use online multiplayer bs bingo game.

Daytrack Github.

An easy to use day journal app to help keep track of weekly/monthly progress.

Pomodoro Github.

An easy to use and visually pleasing PWA timer app.